Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original Accession, 1920-1980
  - General Files
    - Smith, Joel P. - Speeches and articles, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Social counselor, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Social regulations, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Social regulations - History (1), Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Social regulations - History (2), Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Social regulations, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Social regulations, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Sparkle committee, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Special services (Draft counseling), Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Speech and drama department, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Speech Association, Undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sponsor grievances, Undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Sponsors, Undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Sponsor weekend, Undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Spring sing, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Club of Los Angeles, Undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Electronics Labs, Undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Employees Association, Undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Employees Organization, Undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Homeowners Association, Undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Institute for Behavior Counseling, Undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Stanford Judicial Council Revision, Undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Stanford University Libraries, Undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Stanford Mothers Club - Los Angeles, Undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Mothers Club of Washington - Scholarship, Undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Photography Club, Undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Research Institute, Undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Sailing Association, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Student Agencies, Inc., Undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, Undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow leadership conference, 1966 September 27 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Stanford United Ministry, Undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Stanford United Ministry, Undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Stanford University Now, Undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Stanford village, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Stanford volunteers, Undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - State Constitution revision, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Stern houses, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Stern, 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Serra demonstration house, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Strawberry network, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Student affairs and services committee, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Student appointments to committees, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Student correspondence and recommendations, 1968-1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Student discipline proposals, Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Student faculty board, Undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Student faculty commission, Undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Student faculty employment committee, Undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Student-faculty recreation board, Undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Student faculty relations, 1954-1956 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Student faculty relations, 1956-1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Student financial manager, 1950-1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Student financial manager, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Student financial manager, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Student financial manager, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Student health insurance, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Student records, 1962-1969 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Student relations, 1969-1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Student rights, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Student services permit, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Student services task force, Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Students for a Democratic Society, 1965-1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Students' Organizations Fund, 1951-1955 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Students' Organizations Fund, 1955-1963 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Students' Organizations Fund, 1964-1965 August (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Students' Organizations Fund, 1965 September-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Studio Watts Workshop, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Study of Education at Stanford, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Summer camp, Undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Summer festivals, Undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Summer housing, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Summer projects, Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Summer session, Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Sunday events, Committee on, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Systems analysis, Undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - T - General correspondence, Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Table grapes, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Task Force (Use of university facilities), Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Task Force Committee - Ref., Undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Teachers College book prize (annual), Undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters, Undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Toyon Hall, Undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Trailers, Undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Transfer students, Undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Tresidder Union, Undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - TMU, Ref., 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - U - General correspondence, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Union residence, Undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - United Campus Christian Ministry, Undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - United States Naval Academy, Undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Universities - General, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Brigham Young University, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - University of California (Statewide), Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - University of California at Berkeley, Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - University of California at Los Angeles, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Yale University, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - University lectures, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - University lectures, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - University lectures, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - University relations, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - University relations - S. Ca. office, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Upward Bound, Undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Urban studies, Program on, Undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - V - General correspondence, Undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Vandalism, Costs of campus, Undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Vargas memorial fund, Undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer services center, Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - W - General correspondence, Undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Watch list, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Wert committee, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Western Deans Conference, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Wilbur houses, Undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Women, Undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Woodrow Wilson scholarship, Undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - WRA, Undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - X - General correspondence, Undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - X (Donna's) - Confidential recommendations, Undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - X, Undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Y - General correspondence, Undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - YOP (Youth Opportunity Prg.), Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Yell leaders, 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Yell leaders, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, Undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Young Democrats, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Young Republicans, Undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Z - General correspondence, Undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Zotts, Undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files
    - Chronological files, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Chronological files, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Committees
    - Academic affairs, Student-faculty advisory committee on, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Advising and the Freshman year, Subcommittee on, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Athletics, Committee on, Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Buildings and grounds, Committee on, Undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Committee structure of the University, Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Deans advisory committee, Undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Fifteen, Committee of, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Finance, Committee on, Undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Freshman year, Sub-committee on the, and advising committee on undergrad studies, Robert E. Freelen, Undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - General studies, Committee on, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Health committee, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Investments, Committee on, Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Judicial system, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Land development, Committee on, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Low cost housing committee, Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Minority affairs, University committee on, Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - National Student Association, 1947-1956 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - National Student Association, 1957-1962 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - National Student Association, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - National Student Association, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Committee on new undergrad living ideas, Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Overseas scholarship commission (IIR), Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Palo Alto medical clinic - Stanford liaison committee, Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Parents day, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Parents day, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Parents day, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Parents day, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Parents day, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Parents day, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Parents day, 1954-1964 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Parents day, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Parents day, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Parents day, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Parents day, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Peace Corps, 1961-1966 August (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Peace Corps, 1966-1967 January (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Placement service, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Planning and development committee, Undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Planning and development committee, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Policy - General, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Pre-reg, 1948-1956 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Pre-reg, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Pre-reg, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Pre-reg, 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Pre-reg, 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Pre-reg, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Pre-reg, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Pre-reg, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Pre-reg, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Pre-reg, transfer, 1969 Spring (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pre-reg, transfer, 1969 Winter (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Pre-reg, early and late, Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - President's student advisory committee, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Public events, Committee on (COPE), Undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Public events, Committee on - Policy manual, Undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Public exercises, Committee on, Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Public exercises, Committee on, Subcommittee on standards, Undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Public health committee, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Registrar's advisory committee, Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Registrar's advisory committee, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Residence operating committee, Undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Residence policies (SES), Committee on, Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Selective service, Committee on, Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Services to students, Committee on (COSS), Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Services to students, Presidential committee on (COSS), Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - COSS, Subcommitee on residences, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - COSS, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - COSS, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - COSS, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - COSS, File #1, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - COSS, File #2, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - COSS, File #3, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - COSS, Mayhew report, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Student faculty employment committee, Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Student faculty employment committee, Undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Student financial aid, Committee on, Undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Student hospitalization, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Student hospitalization insurance, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Student participation in university committees, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Tuition and financial aid, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Undergraduate admissions, Committee on, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Undergraduate admissions, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Undergraduate admissions and financial aid, Committee on, Undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Undergraduate council curriculum committee, Undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, File #1, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, File #2, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, File #3, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, File #1, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Undergraduate education, Committee on, File #2, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Undergraduate residence committee, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Undergraduate studies, Committee on and subcommittees (ASSU), Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Union committee, Undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - University policy, Committee on, Undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - University policy, Committee on, 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - University policy, Committee on, Undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Judicial Council minutes and correspondence
    Judicial council material is closed
    - Men's, 1920 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      Closed
    - Men's, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Men's, 1922 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Men's, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Men's, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Men's, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Men's, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Men's, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Men's, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Men's, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Men's, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Men's, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Men's, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Men's, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Men's, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Men's and Women's, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Men's, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Men's and Women's, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Men's and Women's, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Men's and Women's, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Men's, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Men's, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Men's and Women's, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Men's and Women's, 1943 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Men's and Women's, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Men's and Women's, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Men's and Women's, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Men's and Women's, 1947 January-August (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Men's and Women's, 1947 September-December (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Men's and Women's, 1948 January-August (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Men's and Women's, 1948 September-December (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Men's and Women's, 1949 January-July (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Joint, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Joint, 1950-1951 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Joint, 1951-1952 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Joint, 1952-1953 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Women's Council, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Women's Council - History, Undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Women's Council - A-G, Undated; Volume (Box 51)
    - Women's Council - H-N, Undated; Volume (Box 51)
    - Women's Council - Special cases, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Auxiliary committee minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Auxiliary committee minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Council minutes (overseas), 1968-1970 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - General, 1926-1957 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - General, 1958-1964 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - General, 1964-1965 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - General, 1965-1968 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Judicial cases - Dean's disposition, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Interim judicial body, Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Provost's Office and Staff
    - Provost's staff, Undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Staff, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Staff, 1967 January-March (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Staff, 1967 March-April (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Staff, File #1, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Staff, File #2, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Staff, File #3, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Staff, File #1, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Staff, File #2, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Staff, File #1, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Staff, File #2, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Office (Associate), Bacchetti, Undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Office (General), Undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Office (Lyman), Undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Office (Packer), Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous and Confidential
    Miscellaneous and confidential material is closed
    - Placement service, 1961-1965 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Placement service, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Placement service, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Probation, Undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Special appellate board, Undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Confidential file: Discipline subcommittee of the student affairs and services com., Undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Confidential file: Inter-fraternity council, 1946-1961 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Confidential file: Exemption lists for Parents Day, General secretary's office, Undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Confidential file: List of special students for President's office, Undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Confidential file: Women's council minutes (not indexed in black book), Undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence
    - Escondido Village, 1974-1977 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Escondido Village, 1974-1977 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Escondido Village, 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Residences, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Residences, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Residential education, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Residential education, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Residential education, 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Tressider Memorial Union, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous files
    - Black, John D. (Director of research), 1973-1976 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Black, John D. (Director of research), 1973-1976 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Palo Alto/Stanford liaison committee, 1973-1976 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Palo Alto/Stanford liaison committee, 1973-1976 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Shunatoma, Gwen (Asst. Dean of Student Affairs, Director of Native American Affairs), 1974-1976 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Additional Records, 1964-1973; Accession ARCH-1984-019
  - Student Conduct Legislative Council (SCLC), Stanford Judicial Council (SJC), Disruptions, Encina Hall Sit-in, Delta Tau Delta fraternity (haircutting incident), 1968-1971 and undated (Box 1)
  - Fundamental standard commission regarding liquor, Mark Franklin case, SJC, Disruption - Spring 1970 news release, 1964-1971 and undated (Box 2)
  - NASPA, Undated (Box 3)
  - NASPA and McClellan Subcommittee on campus disruption, 1969 and undated (Box 4)
    McClellan Subcommittee on campus disruption material is confidential and sealed.
  - Vice President's group and Cowell Director search, 1967-1973 (Box 5)
  - SDS, Publications - Stonecloud publications, Applied Electronics Laboratory Sit-in, Academic Council meeting disruption, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Assorted Contents, Undated (Box 7)
    Includes files of Wayne Johnson, interim Assistant Dean for Native American affairs; files of Larry Gorospe, Assistant Dean for Native American affairs; files of Harold Boyd pertaining to the BCSC.
  - Assorted Contents, Undated (Box 8)
  - Chicano affairs, early 1970s (Box 9)
  - Assorted Contents, Undated (Box 10)
  - Assorted Contents, Undated (Box 11)
  - Assorted Contents, Undated (Box 12)
  - Chicano affairs, early 1970s (Box 13)
- Additional Records, 1972-1981; Accession ARCH-1984-024
  - C.O.P.E., Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - COSS Subcommittee - Minority affairs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - C.O.S.S., Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student evaluation of teaching committee, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of teaching - minutes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Childcare policy study, Stanford, 1972; Booklet (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Education and employment of women, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee on the education and employment of women in the university, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the education and employment of women in the university, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on the education and employment of women in the university, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Off-campus student center (OCSC), Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - OCSC carpool evaluation, questionnaire and budget, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - OSCS coordinator - resumes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Off-campus student questionnaires, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Survey of off-campus students, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - OCSC flyers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - OCSC informers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - OCSC correspondence, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Graduate student lounge, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - OCSC, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - OCSC financial business, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Committee on the physically limited, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Accessibility surveys, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee on disabled students, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Additional Records, 1974-1978; Accession ARCH-1984-058